{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147862154","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147862154"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" c6a77d76-d00e-437b-981d-d4a7a07a1418"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147863663","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147863663"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" c6a77d76-d00e-437b-981d-d4a7a07a1418"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147864771","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147864771"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" c6a77d76-d00e-437b-981d-d4a7a07a1418"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147872471","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147872471"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" c6a77d76-d00e-437b-981d-d4a7a07a1418"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147896157","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147896157"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" c6a77d76-d00e-437b-981d-d4a7a07a1418"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147896226","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147896225"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" eb16079f-387d-4652-ae9d-835e616c95ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEKEE"," userResponse":" KIPEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147917203","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147917203"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" f07281cf-3e73-416f-a720-b97be469e257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_F_CH_T"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147924699","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147924699"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" f07281cf-3e73-416f-a720-b97be469e257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_F_CH_T"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147934939","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147934939"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" f07281cf-3e73-416f-a720-b97be469e257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_F_CH_T"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147941122","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147941122"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" f07281cf-3e73-416f-a720-b97be469e257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_F_T_E"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147948620","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147948620"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" f07281cf-3e73-416f-a720-b97be469e257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_F_T_E"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147955230","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147955230"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" f07281cf-3e73-416f-a720-b97be469e257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_R_T"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147962779","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147962779"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" f07281cf-3e73-416f-a720-b97be469e257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_R_T"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147973036","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147973036"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" f07281cf-3e73-416f-a720-b97be469e257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_R_T"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147979203","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147979203"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" f07281cf-3e73-416f-a720-b97be469e257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Y_T_H"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147985813","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147985813"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" f07281cf-3e73-416f-a720-b97be469e257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_T_A"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147992407","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147992407"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" f07281cf-3e73-416f-a720-b97be469e257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_T_O_CH"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147999000","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147999000"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" f07281cf-3e73-416f-a720-b97be469e257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_G_L_T"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148006463","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148006463"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" f07281cf-3e73-416f-a720-b97be469e257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_G_L_T"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148013090","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148013090"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" f07281cf-3e73-416f-a720-b97be469e257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_T_V_S"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148020538","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148020538"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" f07281cf-3e73-416f-a720-b97be469e257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_T_V_S"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148030797","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148030797"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" f07281cf-3e73-416f-a720-b97be469e257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_T_V_S"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148036979","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148036979"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" f07281cf-3e73-416f-a720-b97be469e257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_T_H_N"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148043559","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148043559"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" f07281cf-3e73-416f-a720-b97be469e257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_G_T_S"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148051003","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148051003"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" f07281cf-3e73-416f-a720-b97be469e257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_G_T_S"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148058022","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148058021"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" f07281cf-3e73-416f-a720-b97be469e257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_T..T.all.10.rand.say.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_G_T_S"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148072736","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148072735"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" 8c449421-30de-4244-965d-e77e5124cb49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-8-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148078267","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148078267"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" 8c449421-30de-4244-965d-e77e5124cb49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-8-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148083496","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148083496"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" 8c449421-30de-4244-965d-e77e5124cb49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-8-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148088391","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148088391"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" 8c449421-30de-4244-965d-e77e5124cb49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-8-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148093132","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148093132"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" 8c449421-30de-4244-965d-e77e5124cb49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-8-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148100381","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148100381"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" 8c449421-30de-4244-965d-e77e5124cb49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-8-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148108607","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148108607"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" 8c449421-30de-4244-965d-e77e5124cb49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_0-4-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148113198","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148113198"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" 8c449421-30de-4244-965d-e77e5124cb49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_0-4-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148117904","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148117904"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" 8c449421-30de-4244-965d-e77e5124cb49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_0-4-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148124329","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148124328"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" 8c449421-30de-4244-965d-e77e5124cb49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_3-8-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148131535","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148131535"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" 8c449421-30de-4244-965d-e77e5124cb49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_3-8-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148137856","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148137856"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" 8c449421-30de-4244-965d-e77e5124cb49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_3-8-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148143787","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148143787"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" 8c449421-30de-4244-965d-e77e5124cb49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-0-2"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148148530","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148148530"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" 8c449421-30de-4244-965d-e77e5124cb49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_8-1-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148153742","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148153742"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" 8c449421-30de-4244-965d-e77e5124cb49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_8-1-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148158458","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148158458"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" 8c449421-30de-4244-965d-e77e5124cb49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_8-1-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148165873","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148165873"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" 8c449421-30de-4244-965d-e77e5124cb49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-9-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148176454","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148176454"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" 8c449421-30de-4244-965d-e77e5124cb49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_4-7-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148181991","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148181991"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" 8c449421-30de-4244-965d-e77e5124cb49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-4-2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148188365","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148188364"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" 8c449421-30de-4244-965d-e77e5124cb49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-4-2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148196982","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148196982"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" 8c449421-30de-4244-965d-e77e5124cb49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-1-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148203576","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148203576"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" 8c449421-30de-4244-965d-e77e5124cb49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-1-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148212644","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148212643"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" cfcad2eb-5a88-4a1f-ac33-0cccfb838131"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_B-V-T"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148219899","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148219899"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" cfcad2eb-5a88-4a1f-ac33-0cccfb838131"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_F-J-T"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148226146","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148226146"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" cfcad2eb-5a88-4a1f-ac33-0cccfb838131"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_F-J-T"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148230824","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148230824"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" cfcad2eb-5a88-4a1f-ac33-0cccfb838131"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-Z-U"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148232153","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148232153"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" cfcad2eb-5a88-4a1f-ac33-0cccfb838131"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-Z-U"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148243651","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148243651"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" 37bd7b4a-6816-40c4-9b83-177f63441ef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-Z-U"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550148246502","data":{"timestamp":" 1550148246501"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153721"," gameId":" 37bd7b4a-6816-40c4-9b83-177f63441ef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-Z-U"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}